thatstea.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://www.thatstea.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

 ** _Information that you provide on message boards and other user forums:  _**including your username, images, or videos.  Please use caution when posting to messages boards or other forums, as information posted to these portions of our online services is public information.

 ** _Information about your equipment and about your interactions with That’s Tea, and other online services: F_** or example, your Internet protocol or IP address; pages, content, or advertising that you visit within online services (including online services not provided by That’s Tea); or the type and version of your device’s operating system or web browser, your device ID, and in some instances, your device’s location.

 ** _Information that is collected from social networks and publicly available data:  _**if you visit our online services on a device through which you also interact with social networks or if you interact with us through a social media function such as a plug-in (for example, a Facebook “like” button) then you may be permitting us to have on-going access to some information from your social network profile (such as your name, email address, your friend list, photo, age, gender, location, birthday, social networking ID, current city, and the people/sites you follow ). If you don’t want a social network to collect the information about you as described above, or you don’t want a social network to share it with us and other third parties, please review the privacy settings and instructions of the applicable social network before you visit and use our online services.

 ** _Information About Your Video Viewing Behavior:  _**information about your video viewing behavior on our online services (e.g., content viewed and information about the advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on, etc.).

 **Additional information about the information we collect:** We use the comment service “Spot.im” which may collect similar data from you. The service’s privacy policy is available here: [https://spot.im/privacy/](https://www.spot.im/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to collect data like how many users are on the site, which content they’re browsing. The google analytics privacy policy, and what data is collected, and how google uses that data can be provided here: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

## Who we share your data with, and how we share your information

 ** _Service providers that we have retained to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf:_** For example, service providers who offer services including research and analytics; hosting websites, fulfilling transactions, maintaining databases, administering contests, providing technology services and platforms, and processing payments.  These parties are provided only with the personal information or other information they need to perform their functions and can only use and disclose that information as is necessary to perform the services on our behalf, or to comply with legal requirements. We take steps to ensure that third party service providers will take appropriate steps to protect your personal information.

 ** _Social Networks:  _**You may interact with certain features of our online services that cause information to be published to your social networks.  For example, you may click on a Facebook “like” button, which publishes to your Facebook account that you “like” one of our stories or social media posts on other platforms.  On pages of our online services that contain social network functionality, the social network providing the functionality may be able to collect information about you, even if you don’t use that functionality. For example, if a page within our online services contains a Facebook “like” button, Facebook may be able to collect data about your visit to that page, even if you don’t click on the “like” button. To control this sharing of information, please review the privacy policy of the relevant social network and/or log out of it before you use our online services.

 ** _Advertisers, Advertising Networks and Consumer Data Resellers:  _**Some online services, including mobile apps, may be supported with advertising, and collect data to help our online services serve ads.  This helps keep the cost of online services low or free. We work with advertisers and third-party advertising networks and consumer data resellers that buy and/or sell information to other companies for multiple purposes including offering products and services that may interest you. These third parties may receive information about how you interact with content and advertising provided in our online services. These third parties may view, edit or set their own tracking technologies/cookies, which will allow them to collect information about you.

 ** _Sharing of Video Viewing Behavior:_** We may share information (and you agree to this sharing) about the video content you view on our online services with video measurement services, analytics providers and advertising companies, and third party social media sites. This sharing shall continue for two years or until you withdraw your consent. Information that may be passed to video measurement services, analytics providers and advertising companies may be via cookies and tracking technologies.

## How long we retain your data

In this section you should explain how long you retain personal data collected or processed by the web site. While it is your responsibility to come up with the schedule of how long you keep each dataset for and why you keep it, that information does need to be listed here. For example, you may want to say that you keep contact form entries for six months, analytics records for a year, and customer purchase records for ten years.

 **Suggested text:  **If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

We however do not have any sign up services directly on thatstea.com. You may contact websites such as Google.com and Spot.im, Amazon’s Alexa, Facebook, and other social media networks for the collection of your data.

By using this website, and its services, you’re consenting the collection of your data and their privacy polices that these third parties collect.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service through a Third Party on Spot.Im.

## Your contact information

Contact as with any questions or concerns at sendsometea@gmail.com

### How we protect your data

Our site is SSL encrypted. We take measures that the service providers and advertisers we are partnered with that may collect data have data security in place.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

As we do not personally collect your data on this site itself, please go to the links provided in this privacy policy and consult with the third parties about their data breach procedures.

We use Google Analytics, Bandsintown Advertising, Alexa Analytics, Facebook, and other brands that

### What third parties we receive data from

We do not participate in Consumer Data Reselling, we do not buy data. We receive data that Google Analytics provide. From advertisers, we’re able to see what countries have viewed the ads, and how many people have viewed those ads. We are unable to see which ads have been viewed, we are also unable to see which individuals have viewed the ads.

### What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data

We do not practice any automated decision making and/or profiling.
